USS Arizona Collection, 1907-2015 (bulk 1915-1941)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series 1: Photographic Materials, 1915-1962
  - Subseries 3: 8x10 Photographs, circa 1920-1976
    - 1931 USS Arizona Football Team, 84-31-2 (Box 28, Folder 47)
    - Miss Eva Behn, Mrs. WW Ross, Honorable Josephus Daniels, Governor George WP Hunt, Miss Esther Ross at USS Arizona Christening, June 19, 1915, 85-6-2 (Box 28, Folder 48)
  - Subseries 4: Oversize Photographic Material, 1920-1941 December 7
    This subseries is described at the item level. It contains oversize copy negatives and prints that document the ship and her crew in various locales, the Japanese attack on Pearl Harbor on December 7, 1941, as well as the USS Arizona Memorial in Pearl Harbor, Hawaii. Materials of particular note held within this subseries include the christening and launching of the ship on 19 June 1915, and the ship's visit to Guantanamo Bay, Cuba circa 1920. This subseries also contains materials created by Carlos W. Cecil who served on the USS Arizona from 1918-1920. The materials are comprised of mounted black and white photographs with accompanying text and documents which include the 1918 May 16 – 1920 May 20 cruising records of the USS Arizona and USS Nevada. Certain materials are duplicated in other series within the collection. Item titles contain a three digit accession number assigned by the University of Arizona Student Union upon donation of the item. This number consists of a tripartite system that consists of three parts that refer to the year of the item’s acquisition, the transaction number of that year, and the individual specimen number within that transaction.
    - Crew of USS Arizona on Deck, copy negative from Carlos W. Cecil, 71-4-4, circa 1920 (Box 29, Item 1)
    - Crew of USS Arizona on Deck, copy negative from Carlos W. Cecil, 71-4-4, circa 1920 (Box 29, Item 2)
    - Multiple negatives of Airplanes on USS Arizona Deck and Cruising Record, copy negative from Carlos W. Cecil, 71-4-5, circa 1920 (Box 29, Item 3)
    - Multiple negatives of Airplanes on USS Arizona Deck and Cruising Record, copy negative from Carlos W. Cecil, 71-4-5, copy, circa 1920 (Box 29, Item 4)
    - Unidentified Ships at Sea and Cruising Record, copy negative from Carlos W. Cecil, 71-4-6, circa 1920 (Box 29, Item 5)
    - Unidentified Ships at Sea and Cruising Record, copy negative from Carlos W. Cecil, 71-4-6, copy, circa 1920 (Box 29, Item 6)
    - Unidentified Captains and Officers on USS Arizona Deck, 81-3-1, copy negative; Six Images from Guantanamo Bay, Cuba, 71-4-7, copy negative, circa 1920 (Box 29, Item 7)
    - Unidentified Captains and Officers on USS Arizona Deck, 81-3-1, copy negative; Six Images from Guantanamo Bay, Cuba, 71-4-7, copy negative, copy, circa 1920 (Box 29, Item 8)
    - Negative of 71-4-5, 71-4-6, undated (Box 29, Item 9)
    - Negative of 71-4-4, 71-4-7, 81-3-1, undated (Box 29, Item 10)
    - Crew of USS Arizona on Deck, 77-7-1, 1924 (Box 29, Item 11)
    - Crew of USS Arizona on Deck, 77-7-1, Copy, 1924 (Box 29, Item 11A)
    - Mast of USS Arizona Engulfed in Flames during Pearl Harbor Attack, 84-27-1a, 1941 December 7 (Box 29, Item 12)
    - Mast of USS Arizona Falling during Pearl Harbor Attack, 84-27-1b, 1941 December 7 (Box 29, Item 13)
    - USS Arizona Mast Coming Down During Pearl Harbor Attack, 84-27-1c, 1941 December 7 (Box 29, Item 14)
    - USS Arizona Mast Engulfed in Flames during Pearl Harbor Attack, 84-27-1d, 1941 December 7 (Box 29, Item 15)
    - USS Arizona off Pearl Harbor, T.H., 84-27-2a, circa 1941 (Box 29, Item 16)
    - Japanese Running Bombing Drill, 84-27-2b, circa 1941 (Box 29, Item 17)
    - Japanese Photograph of Destruction at Pearl Harbor, 84-27-2c, circa 1941 (Box 29, Item 18)
    - Fleet in Panama Canal, USS Arizona in South End of Gaillard Cut. Pedro Miguel Lock in the Distance, 1921 February 23 (Box 29, Item 19)
    - The Last Instance of Peace Pearl Harbor, 7:55 a.m., Dec. 7, 1941, Map, 84-29-17 (Box 29, Item 20)
    - Portrait of Sailor G. Hollowell who was killed on board USS Arizona During Attack on Pearl Harbor, 66-1-1, circa 1941 (Box 29, Item 21)
    - USS Arizona Mast Falling during Pearl Harbor Attack, 84-27-18, 1941 December 7 (Box 29, Item 22)
    - First USS Arizona Crew on deck of Ship, 84-26-110, 1916 (Box 29, Item 23)
    - USS Bennington Paying Tribute at USS Arizona Memorial, Pearl Harbor, HI, 84-28-16, circa 1963 (Box 29, Item 24)
    - USS Arizona Fourth Anniversary Ball, Hotel Astor, New York, November 16, 1920, 68-9-1, copy (Box 29, Item 25)
    - USS Arizona at the Brooklyn Bridge, Departing New York as Part of Escort for President Wilson on His Way to Paris Peace Conference, 71-4-1, From the Archives of Carlos Wilfred Cecil, copy, 1918 December 13 (Box 29, Item 26)
    - USS Arizona at the Brooklyn Bridge, Departing New York as Part of Escort for President Wilson on His Way to Paris Peace Conference, 71-4-1, From the Archives of Carlos Wilfred Cecil, copy, 1918 December 13 (Box 29, Item 27)
    - USS Arizona Engineering Crew Posed by Gun Turret, 84-26-111, circa 1928 (Box 29, Item 28)
    - Wall of Names of those who perished on the USS Arizona during Pearl Harbor Attack with Wreath, 84-28-13, circa 1963 (Box 30, Item 1)
    - Two Unidentified Marines Standing Guard at Wall of Names of those who perished on the USS Arizona during Pearl Harbor Attack, 84-28-10, circa 1963 (Box 30, Item 2)
    - Mrs. Ester Ross Hogan Christening Arizona II, Honolulu, HI, 77-5-2, 1977 October 17 (Box 30, Item 3)
    - Two Unidentified Marines Standing Guard at USS Arizona Memorial, Pearl Harbor, HI, 84-28-3, circa 1963 (Box 30, Item 4)
    - USS Arizona in Navy Yard, San Pedro, CA, Red E on Stack Awarded for Efficiency of Conservation of Fuel Oil, 76-6-2, circa 1927 (Box 30, Item 5)
    - Training Crew at Sand Diego Naval Training Center before being sent for Duty on USS Arizona, 85-9-5, 1936 (Box 30, Item 6)
    - USS Arizona Main Foremast Coming out of San Francisco Bay, 84-26-10, circa 1935 (Box 30, Item 7)
    - USS Arizona Launched at the New York Navy Yard, 84-10-1, copy, 1915 June 19 (Box 30, Item 8)
    - Platoon 86 CR White CAM September 27, 1930, color tinted print, 77-3-33 (Box 30, Item 9)
    - USS Arizona at Sea with Crew on Deck, 76-6-1, 1917 (Box 30, Item 10)
    - USS Arizona Passing Statue of Liberty, New York City, NY, 77-7-2, 1927 (Box 30, Item 11)
    - USS Arizona Officers and Crew on Deck of Ship, San Francisco, CA, 1928, 68-4-1 (Box 30, Item 12)
    - USS Arizona at Sea with Unidentified Ships in Background, circa 1927 (Box 30, Item 13)
    - USS Arizona Fourth Anniversary Ball, Hotel Astor, New York, November 16, 1920, 68-9-1 (Box 30, Item 14)
    - Aerial View of USS Arizona Sunk in Pearl Harbor, HI, 84-28-17, circa 1941 December 7 (Box 30, Item 15)
    - USS Arizona Memorial, Pearl Harbor, HI, 84-28-4, circa 1963 (Box 30, Item 16)
    - USS Arizona Memorial, Pearl Harbor, HI, 64-6-1, Copy, circa 1963 (Box 30, Item 17)
    - Arizona Delegation to Christen Battleship USS Arizona at the White House – June 18, 1915, Twenty-five people in photograph including: Arizona Governor George W.P. Hunt, President Woodrow Wilson, and Senator H.F. Ashurst, 85-6-1, copy (Box 30, Item 18)
    - USS Arizona Memorial Plaque, Pearl Harbor, HI, 84-4-1, circa 1963 (Box 30, Item 19)
    - USS Arizona Launched at the New York Navy Yard, 84-10-1, 1915 June 19 (Box 31, Item 1)
    - USS Arizona Memorial, Pearl Harbor, HI, 84-28-4, Copy, circa 1963 (Box 31, Item 2)
    - USS Arizona at Sea, 93-30, undated (Box 31, Item 3)
    - USS Arizona Mast Coming Down During Pearl Harbor Attack, 54-1-1, 1941 December 7 (Box 31, Item 4)
    - USS Arizona at Sea, undated (Box 31, Item 5)
    - USS Arizona Memorial, Pearl Harbor, HI, 64-6-1, copy, circa 1963 (Box 31, Item 6)
    - Official Navy Photograph of USS Arizona at Sea, Broadside View, 68-6-1, 1935 (Box 31, Item 7)
    - Aerial View of USS Arizona Sunk in Pearl Harbor, HI, 84-28-12, circa 1941 December 7 (Box 31, Item 8)
    - Original USS Arizona Memorial Showing Navy Launch, Bridge and Flag, Pearl Harbor, HI, 58-7-1, circa 1958 (Box 31, Item 9)
    - USS Arizona in Panama Canal, 87-2-1, circa 1938 (Box 31, Item 10)
    - Sunset View of USS Arizona Memorial, 64-1-5, color print, 1965 July 14 (Box 31, Item 11)
    - Seven Photograph sequence of Plane Trials on board USS Arizona - U.S. Navy Shore Based Airplane on Beach, 71-4-5a; Airplane #5756 Aboard USS Arizona Turret, 71-4-5b; Airplane on USS Arizona Wood Plank Runway, 71-4-5c; Airplane Crash on USS Arizona, 71-4-5d; USS Arizona Airplane Crash Scene, 71-4-5e; USS Arizona Plane Crash Salvage, 71-4-5f; Piece of Arizona 5756 Airplane Wing Covering, 71-4-5g; Collected by Carlos W. Cecil with Descriptions Written in Cecil's Hand, 1920 (Box 32, Item 1)
    - Six Photograph Sequence of Shipboard Activities - Loading Torpedoes before going out on Convoy Duty, 71-4-7a; USS Arizona at Sea Ready to Start a Convoy Run, 71-4-7b; Anti-Submarine Patrol Observation Balloon in Flight, 71-4-7c; Hauling Down Anti-Submarine Patrol Observation Balloon, 71-4-7d; Aerial View of USS Arizona Deck with Men in Formation, 71-4-7e; USS Arizona at Sea Riding At Anchor, 71-4-7f, circa Collected by Carlos W. Cecil with Descriptions Written in Cecil's Hand, circa 1920 (Box 32, Item 2)
    - USS Arizona Crew and Officers on Deck, 81-3-1, 1933 (Box 32, Item 3)
      Copy of 77-3-32, held in box 32 item 6.
    - Officers and Crew on USS Arizona Deck, Guantanamo Bay, Cuba, 71-4-4, From the Archives of Carlos Wilfred Cecil, circa 1920 (Box 32, Item 5)
    - USS Arizona Crew and Officers on Deck, 77-3-32, 1933 (Box 32, Item 6)
    - Atlantic Fleet, 7th Division at Sea, New York City, NY, May, 1920; USS Arizona, USS Nevada Cruising Records Compiled by Carlos W. Cecil, 1918 May 16 – 1920 May 20, 71-4-6 (Box 32, Item 7)
    - Framed USS Arizona Memorial Poster, 69-1-1, undated (Box 32, Item 6)
      Item on permanent exhibit as part of the USS Arizona Exhibit located at the University of Arizona Student Union Memorial Center.
- Series 2: Documents and Scrapbooks, 1907-2005
  This series contains documents that detail the history of the ship and the lives of her crew as well as materials documenting the USS Arizona Memorial in Pearl Harbor, Hawaii. Materials within this series include books, a Continuous Service Certificate dating from 1941 issued to Andrew Jackson Bowen, a notebook from 1939 belonging to William D. Osborne, programs for sporting events, religous services, and other activities on board ship, cards, invitations, certificates, ship logs, crew rosters, listings of crew and personnel, USS Arizona Memorial materials including an architectural deck plan held in box 42, newspapers, magazines, sheet music, and copies of the At Em' Arizona newsletter and other materials that were generated during the ship's lifespan. Also included within this series are scrapbooks by various sailors and Marines who served on the ship. These scrapbooks contain materials that date from around the 1920s-1930s and contain newspaper and magazine articles, black and white photographs, documents, and ephemera. Item poses a three digit accession number written on the verso, which was assigned by the University of Arizona Student Union upon donation of the item. This number consists of a tripartite system that consists of three parts that refer to the year of the item’s acquisition, the transaction number of that year, and the individual specimen number within that transaction.
  - Pearl Harbor Attack, Lott, Arnold S, 84-19-12 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Volume Listing Names, Rank, File Numbers, Next of Kin for Navy Servicemen on Board and / or Attached to the USS Arizona, 1941 December 7 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - USS Arizona (BB 39), Friedman, Norman, Baker, Arthur D. III, Lott, Arnold, S., 84-19-8, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Arizona's Heart Beats,, 85-7-1, circa 1985 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Pearl Harbor and the USS Arizona Memorial: A Pictorial History,, Wisniewski, Richard A., 84-19-7, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - The Story of the Battleship Arizona,, Arizona Highways, Vol. XXIX, no.9, 84-19-9, 1953 September (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - East Wind Rain: A Pictorial History of the Pearl Harbor Attack,, Cohen, Stan, 84-31-1, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Neptune's Domain: USS Arizona Crosses the Equator,, May 20, 1936, 84-1-1 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Ship and Gun-Drills, United States Navy, 1907 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Shipmates Forever Illustrated by Eddie Piper, 84-19-1, 1936 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Neptune's Domain: USS Arizona Crosses the Equator,, May 20, 1936, 84-19-4 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Holy Bible, New York Bible Society, 61-1-1 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Willian D. Osborne, FC 1st Class Notebook, circa 1939 (Box 33a, Folder 1)
  - Andrew Jackson Bowen, Jr. Continuous Service Certificate, circa 1941 (Box 33a, Folder 2)
  - La Historia de Pearl Harbor, Informacion y Fotographias Autenticas del ataque a Pearl Harbor 7 de Diciembre de 1941, Capitan William T. Rice (Box 33a, Folder 3)
  - The USS Arizona Memorial: Beyond Arizona's Border...But Forever in its Memory, James Tallon, Arizona Highways, Vol. 57, No. 8 (Box 33a, Folder 4)
  - Remembering Pearl Harbor: The Story of the USS Arizona Memorial,, Slackman, Michael, 84-39-1, 1984 (Box 33a, Folder 5)
  - USS Arizona Memorial Services Guest Book, 1959-1982 (Box 33a, Folder 6)
  - Day of Infamy: The Human Drama of Pearl Harbor,, Life Magazine, 84-19-6, 1956 December 3 (Box 33a, Folder 7)
  - On to Pearl Harbor and Beyond,, Jackson, Charles L., 84-30-1, 1982 (Box 33a, Folder 8)
  - USS Arizona Snapshots Photograph Album, Donated by J.E. Kelpin, 71-1-1 (empty), circa 1927-1928 (Box 33a, Folder 9)
    J.E. Kelpin served on board the USS Arizona from 1927-1928. Scrapbook originally held items 71-1-2 – 71-1-237 (see boxes 7 – 12)
  - Horace P. Greer Scrapbook, 1930-1980 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Scrapbook is comprised of newspaper clippings, magazine articles, documents, and ephemera that document Greer's career in the U.S. Navy and the history of the USS Arizona and other U.S. Navy battleships.
  - USS Arizona Scrapbook Pages, circa 1935-1972 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    Pages contains newspaper clippings and magazine articles that document the history of the USS Arizona and other U.S. Navy battleships.
  - USS Arizona Sick Log Scrapbook, Photocopy, 1924 September-October (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - USS Arizona Smooth Log, 1917 April 06 – 1919 August 07 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - USS Arizona Christmas Cards, 1934-1939, undated (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - At Em' Arizona, Christmas, 1922, Our Navy, July, 1935 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - USS Arizona Invitations, 1924-1940 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - USS Arizona Programs and Menus, 1919-1941 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Private Bill E. Parrish, U.S. Marine Corp. 7th Division Scrapbook, 1938-1939 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    Scrapbook contains black and white photographs, documents, correspondence, newspaper clippings, magazine articles, ephemera, and greeting cards that document Parrish's career in the U.S. Navy and the history of the USS Arizona and other U.S. Navy battleships. Also contained are materials documenting Axis powers military campaigns in Europe.
  - William Charles Austin Scrapbook, 1930-1931 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    Scrapbook contains documents, black and white photographs of sailors, relatives and friends, US Navy battleships, USS Arizona athletics teams, interior and exterior views of the USS Arizona, and aircraft.
  - William Charles Austin Scrapbook, 1932-1934 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    Scrapbook contains newspaper clippings and magazine articles documenting the USS Arizona. This scrapbook also contains black and white photographs, postcards, documents, programs, and ephemera documenting the USS Arizona and other U.S. Navy battleships.
  - William Charles Austin Documents, 1930-1935 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    Folder contains Austin's Continuous Service Certificate, a U.S. Navy Honorable Discharge Certificate, and U.S. Navy Training Certificates. Also included is an undated black and white postcard of the USS Arizona at sea, and USS Arizona patches.
  - Kenneth Hargraves Correspondence, 1941 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    Folder contains photocopies of correspondence Kenneth Hargraves sent to his parents from Wapato, Washington.
  - USS Arizona and Related Ship Documents, 1915-1941 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    Folder contains permissions slips, a ticket to the USS Arizona launch, 1915 June 19, request and issue slips, writings, USS Arizona Instructions for writing the Log, instruction documents, day's orders, correspondence concerning the Neptunus Rex Ceremony, a payroll for the Marine Detachment on the USS Arizona, December, 1941, Muster Roll of Officers and Enlisted men of the US Marine Corps, 1 December – 31 December. 1941, and other documents related to the USS Arizona, the USS Savannah, and USS Helena.
  - USS Arizona and Related Envelopes and Postcards, 1931-1942 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper Clippings Related to the USS Arizona, 1919-1945 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Navy Honorable Discharge Certificates, 1927-1939 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Navy Training Course Certificates issued to William A. Watkins, 1931-1936 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - USS Arizona Enlisted Men Rosters, 1941 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Notices of Dead and Missing Enlisted USS Arizona Crew Members, 1941-1942 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - The Arizonian Newsletter, 1918, 1929 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - At Em' Arizona Newsletter, 1919-1934 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - At Em' Arizona Newsletter, 1934-1936 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - At Em' Arizona Newsletter, 1937-1939 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Radio Press News Newsletter, 1934-1937 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - USS Arizona Memorial Ceremony, 1950-1956 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - USS Arizona Memorial Ceremony, 1955 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - USS Arizona Memorial Ceremony, 1956 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - USS Arizona Memorial Ceremony, 1957 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - USS Arizona Memorial Ceremony, 1958 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - USS Arizona Memorial Ceremony, 1959 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - USS Arizona Memorial Ceremony, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - USS Arizona Memorial Ceremony, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - USS Arizona Memorial Ceremony, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - USS Arizona Memorial Ceremony, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - USS Arizona Memorial Ceremony, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - USS Arizona Memorial Ceremony, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - USS Arizona Memorial Ceremony, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - USS Arizona Memorial Ceremony, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - USS Arizona Memorial Ceremony, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - USS Arizona Memorial Ceremony, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - USS Arizona Memorial Ceremony, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - USS Arizona Memorial Ceremony, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - USS Arizona Memorial Ceremony, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - USS Arizona Memorial Ceremony, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - USS Arizona Memorial Ceremony, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - USS Arizona Memorial Ceremony, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - USS Arizona Memorial Ceremony, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - USS Arizona Memorial Ceremony, 1977 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - USS Arizona Memorial Ceremony, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - USS Arizona Memorial Ceremony, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - USS Arizona Memorial Ceremony, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - USS Arizona Memorial Ceremony, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - USS Arizona Memorial Ceremony, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - USS Arizona Memorial Ceremony, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - USS Arizona Memorial Ceremony, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - USS Arizona Memorial Ceremony, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - USS Arizona Annual Reunion Programs, 1960-1963 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - USS Arizona Memorial Service Programs, 1955-1979 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - USS Arizona Memorial Service Programs, 1980-2005 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - USS Arizona Reunion Association Annual Reunion Programs, 1978-2005 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - 25th Anniversary of the Attack on Pearl Harbor Press Kit, 1966 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Battling Bandsmen, Nelson, Gary L., undated (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Written Reports about the USS Arizona, 1996-2000 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Crossing the Line, USS Arizona, July 1940, 84-8-1 (Box 40, Item 1)
  - Echoes of Infamy, The Orange County Register, Sunday, 1991 December 8 (Box 40, Item 2)
  - Fifty Years After WWII, The Orange County Register, 1989 Sunday, August 27 (Box 40, Item 3)
  - Congress Declares War!, The Orange County Register, 1991 Sunday, December 8 (Box 40, Item 4)
  - Japan Wars on U.S., Chicago Herald American, 1941 December 8 (Box 40, Item 5)
  - Congress Votes War in Half Hour, The Rock Island Argus, 1941 December 8 (Box 40, Item 6)
  - Japan Attacks U.S.!, Chicago Daily Tribune, 1941 December 8 (Box 40, Item 7)
  - War! Oahu Bombed by Japanese Planes, Honolulu Star-Bulletin, 1941 December 7 (Box 40, Item 8)
  - The United States of America Purple Heart Certificate awarded to James William Horrocks, 58-3-2, 1943 November 22 (Box 40, Item 9)
  - Muster of the Lowly Landlubbers, USS Arizona Crew Roster, 77-2-1f, Copy, undated (Box 40, Item 10)
  - Letter of Commendation for James William Horrocks signed by Franklin D. Roosevelt, 58-3-4, 1941 (Box 40, Item 11)
  - Domain of Neptunus Rex Ceremony, 77-2-1a-e, Copy, 1936 May 20 (Box 40, Item 12)
  - Uncle Sam's Ships, Words and Music by Daisy M. Erd, Sheet Music, 1917 (Box 40, Item 13)
  - Here Comes the Navy, Words by Lt. Comdr. Clarence P. Oakes, U.S.N.R., Sheet Music, 1934 (Box 40, Item 14)
  - Anchors Aweigh: The Song of the Navy, by Charles A. Zimmermann, Sheet Music, 1935 (Box 40, Item 15)
  - Bell Bottom Trousers, Words and Music by Moe Jaffe, Sheet Music, 1944 (Box 40, Item 16)
  - Hail, the Navy!, Words and Music by Rosetta Perry Gibbon, Sheet Music, 1932 (Box 40, Item 17)
  - Saboteurs Land Here! Britain, Australia Declare War! The Honolulu Advertiser, 1941 December 8 (Box 40, Item 18)
  - Neither Kimmel Nor Short Showed Appreciation of Responsibilities Vested in Them, World-Herald, Omaha, Nebraska, 1942, January 25 (Box 40, Item 19)
  - Hymn to the United States Navy, by Ernest Charles, Sheet Music, 1943 (Box 40, Item 19)
  - Neptunus Rex Ceremony Photographs, Roster of Neptunus Rex Party, Donated by Carlos Wilfred Cecil, 71-4-8, 1921 January 24 (Box 40, Item 20)
  - Fleet Problem XIX, 1938 Map, 84-36-2 (Box 40, Item 21)
  - Neptunus Rex Ceremony Certificate Issued to Vincent Henry Eberhart, 68-6-1, 1940 July 24 (Box 40, Item 22)
  - Neptunus Rex Ceremony Certificate Issued to Vincent Henry Eberhart, 68-6-1, Copy, 1940 July 24 (Box 40, Item 23)
  - Attack on Pearl Harbor Map, 84-27-20, undated (Box 40, Item 24)
  - The Mystery of Pearl Harbor, Los Angeles Examiner, 1942 March 1 (Box 40, Item 25)
  - State has Floating Namesake, Westward, 83-2-4, 1982 December 17 (Box 40, Item 26)
  - Instrument of Surrender, 74-4-1, copy, 1945 September 02 (Box 40, Item 27)
  - Domain of Neptunus Rex Certificate Issued to William A. Watkins, undated (Box 40, Item 28)
  - USS Arizona Thanksgiving Dinner Menu, 76-3-1, 1918 November 28 (Box 40, Item 29)
  - Recording of USS Arizona Bell Peal, Phonograph Record, 84-13-1, undated (Box 40, Item 30)
  - Attack on Pearl Harbor Map, 84-27-20, Copy, undated (Box 40, Item 31)
  - USS Arizona Memorial Architectural Deck Plan, 1960 May 17 (Box 41, Item 1)
- Series 3: Objects, circa 1911-1983